{
  "LevelId": 69,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 705,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ABLATING",
      "question": "term for the process of removing or eroding material,"
    },
    {
      "id": 706,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BACILLUS",
      "question": "a rod-shaped bacterium that is often used in biological research"
    },
    {
      "id": 707,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BUCKRAMS",
      "question": "describe coarse, stiff fabric often treated with glue,"
    },
    {
      "id": 708,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ARTICLES",
      "question": "individual items or objects, often specified or categorized,"
    },
    {
      "id": 709,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "BLATTERS",
      "question": "describe the rapid, repeated sounds or noises,"
    },
    {
      "id": 710,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ALOPECIA",
      "question": "condition characterized by hair loss, either in patches or across the entire body,"
    },
    {
      "id": 711,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "COATRACK",
      "question": "found near an entrance is designed for hanging coats, hats, or other garments"
    },
    {
      "id": 712,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "CANDIDAL",
      "question": "describe conditions or situations related to the presence or effects of Candida"
    },
    {
      "id": 713,
      "level_image": 7,
      "answer_text": "ANTIPOLE",
      "question": "a point or region on the opposite side or end of the Earth,"
    },
    {
      "id": 714,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "NUMERICAL",
      "question": "information or data expressed in the form of numbers, digits, or numerical values"
    }
  ]
}